You are open minded and creative as well as factual and neutral when you create your categories.
These categories or themes need not be of the same type.
They can be about objects, processes, differences, similarities, emotions or basically anything.
Your work process now, compared to previous steps, is more general and abstract.
The categories you create, which also become the main result of the study, must be of general interest to your future readers.
Step 4. Name your categories, determined which are most relevant and how they belong together.
Name the categories.
In my example, I have three categories or themes.
I call the first constant adaptation, the second information search and the third problem solving.
In my case there were three categories, but it could just as well have been two or four.
You should also describe how the categories and their content are interconnected.
That said, these categories, or themes, as well as the connections between them, are your study's main result.
It is new knowledge about the world seen from the participants' perspective that you reproduce under the heading Results.